Guide to the Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
- Series II. Assignments
  - Sheet #24: Daphne Roe/Prof. Nut. Sci., Frames 2a-12a; Steve Leigh/Dir. Class Affairs & Alumni Affairs-Frames 13-29, Aug. 1983; 950; 26 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #25: Nell Mondv/Prof. Nut. Sci.-Office scenes and lab scenes, Aug. 1983; 950; 27 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #26: Robert Schwartz (CEH Alumnus) speaking at Mallott Hall on business careers, Oct. 1983; 950; 8 (Box 21)
  - Sheets #27 & 28: Visiting Minority Faculty in Faculty Commons, MVR, Oct. 1983; 950; 45 (Box 21)
  - Mayor Koch visiting Cornell Campus and Empire Farm Days, Aug. 1982; 951; 42 (Box 21)
  - Student Registration, Orientation, Aug. 1982; 952; 76 (Box 21)
  - Group Portraits of Eastman Rice and Woodford Speech Contest finalists, Nov. 1982; 953; 8 (Box 21)
  - HE Forum, Sheet #1: Windows and doorways around Ithaca, NY, Dec. 1982; 954; 36 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #2: Photos of interior of Virginia Thompson house, Dec. 1982; 954; 37 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #3: Kieth Bryant in his office/CEH, Dec. 1982; 954; 7 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #4-5: Satellite Antennae, Dec. 1982; 954; 12 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #6: John Condry children working with home computer, Dec. 1982; 954; 35 (Box 21)
  - Sheets #7 & 8: Martha DeLyra's home (interior shots), Dec. 1982; 954; 40 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #9: Cynthia Froggett/Grad Student in Human Ecology, Dec. 1982; 954; 10 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #10: Family in front of partially constructed home (David Lehman, Stephanie, Kate Eisenberg and Lisa Ensenburg), Dec. 1982; 954; 35 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #11: Office portrait of Mary Purchase, Dec. 1982; 954; 17 (Box 21)
  - Sheets #12 & 13: Paul Eshelman interview, Jan. 1982; 954; 47 (Box 21)
  - Sheets #14 & 15: Computer Communications Home and Office of Suzanne Broderick, Feb. 1983; 954; 41 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #16: Relating game in MVR Auditorium, Mar. 1983; 954; 13 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #17: Madeliene Holzer-Lecturer in Human Ecology and Coord. For NYC Field Study, Frames 1-19; Charles McClintock--Associate Prof. Of HSS, Mar. 1983; 954; 36 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #18: Florence Cherry--Senior Ext. Associate in HDFS, Frames 9-17; Gret Atkin--Ext. Associate in DEA, Frames 18-36, Mar. 1983; 954; 28 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #19: Girl at computer table in DEA Gallery, Apr. 1983; 954; 18 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #20: Human Ecology Group Interview, July 1983; 954; 19 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #21: Michelle Whitham, Dave Riley, Mon Cochran, Dorothy Torre, Don Barr, July 1983; 954; 21 (Box 21)
  - Sheets #22 & 23: IACC Day Care children at play and with teachers at Farmer's Market and in rooms, Oct. 1983; 954; 49 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #24: Pat Patten-Steward and class in Elmira Free Academy in Elmira, NY, Nov. 1983; 954; 23 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #25: Pat Ziegler in her office in MVR, Dec. 1983; 954; 10 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #26: Polly Spedding in front of white house on Triphammer Road (Future home of Cornell Infant Day Care Center), Dec. 1983; 954; 10 (Box 21)
  - Sheets #27 & 28: Peewee Hockey at Lynah Rink, Dec. 1983; 954; 79 (Box 21)
  - Sheets # 29 & 30: Jonah Nerzak, Peter Nerzak and Nancy Neilsen, Dec. 1983; 954; 23 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #31: Ginny Vanderslice in her office in MVR, Apr. 1984; 954; 10 (Box 21)
  - Cooperative Extension Awareness Program, Sheet #1: Electric Mail Terminal in Cindy Noble's office and Dairy Store (Lab testing of milk), Oct. 1982; 955; 15 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #2: Broom County Dairy and meeting, Oct. 1982; 955; 9 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #3: Corn shots on Moravia farm and meetings, Oct. 1982; 955; 28 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #4: Shel Drake, NY; Grapes and grape harvesting, Oct. 1982; 955; 36 (Box 21)
  - Reception for Chinese delegation, Dec. 9, 1982; 956; 48 (Box 21)
  - Peter Gregory studying toxins in potatoes in research lab (electronic instruments), Dec. 13, 1982; 957; 11 (Box 21)
  - Dairy Days Award Winners, Dec. 1982; 958; 12 (Box 21)
  - Cooperative Extension exhibit, Dec. 1982; 959; 21 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #1: Damon Boynton and Dr. LH MacDaniels discussing new manuscript, Jan. 1983; 960; 18 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #2: Stan Warren and Laurie Todd with historical material at his house, Feb. 1983; 960; 37 (Box 21)
  - Bertha Blaker's retirement party, Jan. 1983; 961; 35 (Box 21)
  - BTI Annual Report, general photos around BTI, Feb. 1983; 962; 275 (Box 21)
  - Group portrait--Scholarship winners for Percy-Leon Scholarship and Henry Buckley Scholarship, Feb. 1983; 963; 7 (Box 21)
  - Bio Technology Research, Sheet #1: Research photo of Dr. Kinsella's lab fermenter (Lab Tech operations), Feb. 1983; 964; 117 (entire job) (Box 21)
  - Sheets #2-5: Bio Tech operations research, Feb. 1983; 964; No. of Negs: (Box 21)
  - Emeritus Professor Damon Boynton/Pomology Staff sketch, Feb. 1983; 965; 11 (Box 21)
  - Professor James Boodley/Floriculture portrait, Feb. 1983; 966; 9 (Box 21)
  - Computer given to Ag. Eng. Department by Carrier Corp., Nov. 1982; 967; 8 (Box 21)
  - Home Study Group, Mar. 1983; 968; 23 (Box 21)
  - Dr. David Pimentel in his lab, Mar. 1983; 969; 8 (Box 21)
  - Photos of Mike Thonney in computer class (F & LSQ), Feb. 1983; 970; 27 (Box 21)
  - ALS News, Sheet #1: Dr. Glen Hausfater and grad students reviewing computer sheets at weekly meeting in Mudd Hall, Mar. 1983; 971; 15 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #2: Ronald Gorewit in lab with lab technician/Morr. Hall, Mar. 1983; 971; 26 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #3: Tractor & tree digger donated to college by Romer Holleran of Greenwich, CT., Mar. 1983; 971; 11 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #4: Dean David Call in his office in Roberts Hall, Mar. 1983; 971; 21 (Box 21)
  - Sheets #5 & 6: Gray treefrog used for electrophoretic research and examination of electrophoretic gels, June 1983; 971; 10 (Box 21)
  - Sheets #7 & 8: ALS Alumni Breakfast, June 1983; 971; 61 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #9: Dale Grossman-Lecturer/Ag. Eco. & Comm. Arts, Aug. 1983; 971; 15 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #10: Robert Smith and wife sitting on bench they donated for use on the Ag. Quad, Aug. 1983; 971; 6 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #11: Robert Mortlock--Chairman & Professor of Microbiology sitting at computer and in lab with student, Sept. 1983; 971; 15 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #12: Dr. Frank Liu doing research on apples at Cornell Orchards, Sept. 1983; 971; 4 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #13: Dr. Tom Eisner and Steve Nowicki in lab, Frames 0-19a-20, Sept. 1983; 971; 20 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #13: Schwardt Lab, Frames 27a-30, Sept. 1983; 971; 3 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #13: Anthony Kiszewski doing blackfly research in Schwardt Lab, Frames 31a-36a, Sept. 1983; 971; 7 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #14: ALS student counselor/Anouk Stein, Dec. 1983; 971; 7 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #15: Floriculture Open House/Plant Science with Grace Price, Jan. 1983; 971; 20 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #16: American Indian student--Raymond Forgnier., Mar. 1984; 971; 6 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #17: Frames 1-14, Casey Carr--student counselor. Frames 15-29 John Sheeley in meeting of Executive Meeting of Coll. Of ALS Positive Adoption Council. Frames 30-36, Prof. Fred Buttel/Rural Soc. Teaching a class, Mar. 1984; 971; 36 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #18: American Indian student Ron LaFrance, Mar. 1984; 971; 5 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #19: Mike Kazarinoff--Assistant Prof. In Nutrition doing colin research, Mar. 1984; 971; 11 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #20: American Indian student Ron LaFrance outside by Stone Hall, Apr. 1984; 971; 6 (Box 21)
  - Carol Anderson/Associate Director--Cooperative Extension, Mar. 1973; 972; 19 (Box 21)
  - Students in various situations at the Hillside Children's Center in Rochester, New York, Mar. 1973; 973; 90 (Box 21)
  - Chinese delegation in meeting in Dean David Call's office, Mar. 1973; 974; 26 (Box 21)
  - Staff sketch of Robert Topor in his office, Mar. 1973; 975; 19 (Box 21)
  - Farmhand using computer to handle feed programs for cattle, Mar. 1973; 976; 10 (Box 21)
  - Ed Daugherty at Electron Microscope in Vet Res. Tower, Apr. 1983; 976; 21 (Box 21)
  - Roger Davenport presenting scholarship plaque to George Gavis (student in Ag. Eco.) for the American Greetings Corp., Mar. 1983; 977; 8 (Box 21)
  - Research support staff--Patricia Rollins, Ted Huller, Pat Deeb, Pat Oplinger, Arlene Clair, James Zuiches, Apr. 1983; 978; 52 (Box 21)
  - Images off TV monitor for artists to use as guide. For use in Cooperative Extension Public Awareness Program, Mar. 1983; 979; 28 (Box 21)
  - Physical Restraint Techniques, Apr. 1983; 980; 148 (Box 21)
  - CALS Scholarship donor-recipient reception at Statler Inn (Dean D. Call, Joe Reganstein, Joe King, Nat Crowe, Viola Miller, Wendall Earle), Apr. 1983; 981; 36 (Box 21)
  - Cornell Livestock Show, Apr. 1983; 982; 56 (Box 21)
  - Winter campus scenes taken by Mike Dudzik & Don Albern, Apr. 1983; 983; 60 (Box 21)
  - Hubert Humphrey Fellowship, 1982-1983, May 1983; 984; 6 (Box 21)
  - Dairy Farmers--Introduction to Computing--sponsored by Stueben County Cooperative Extension taken in Addison, NY, May 1983; 985; 31 (Box 21)
  - Dr. Nolan Vandemark with graduate students in his office in Morrison Hall, May 1983; 986; 11 (Box 21)
  - Ag. Retirement photos for Development & Alumni Affairs, Sheet #1: Russ Martin/Comm. Arts, May 1983; 987; 9 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #2: Robert Young--Animal Science--Frames 1a-7a, Ernest Schaufler--Floriculture--Frames 8a-12a; William Kelly--Veg. Crops, Frames 13a-18a; Roger Sandstead--Veg Crops, Frames 19a-28a; James Lawrence--Comm. Arts Frames 29-6a, May 1983; 987; 36 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #3: Vic Stephens/Communication Arts, Frames 1-8a; Harry Everheart/Natural Resources--Frames 6-14; Roger Young/Entomology--Frames 12a-21a, May 1983; 987; 23 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #4: Nolan Vandemark/Animal Science--Frames 1a-11a; Herb Everett/Plant Breeding--Frames 12a-21a, May 1983; 987; 25 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #5: Gordon Cummings/Professor Rural Sociology--Frames 1a-5a; Dr. Adrian Srb/Genetics--Frames 6a-12a, May 1983; 987; 12 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #6: Ed Smith/Entomology/Frames 1-12; Henry Munger/Plant Breeding & Veg. Crops--Frames 13-21; Alexander Davis/Physical Space Operations--Frames 33-37, May 1983; 987; 26 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #7: Carl C. Lowe/Plant Breeding, May 1983; 987; 6 (Box 21)
  - Animal Science students working with animals and working with a computer at Harford Teaching & Research Center, May 1983; 988; 28 (Box 21)
  - Highway School, June 1983; 989; 44 (Box 21)
  - George Broadwell--Summer Fellowship Training Program, June 1983; 990; 87 (Box 21)
  - Agriculture Business Executives/Class room scenes, June 1983; 991; 27 (Box 21)
  - Root soil research/US Soil & Nutrition Lab, June 1983; 992; 55 (Box 21)
  - Human Ecology Annual Photos, Sheet #1: Moncrieff Cochran/Associate Prof. HDFS--Frames 1-6; T. Colin Campbell/Prof. Nut. Sci.--Frames 17-24; Betty Lewis/Asso. Prof. Nut. Sci.--Frames 25-27, June 1983; 993; 27 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #2: Anne B. Shlay/Asst. Prof. CEH--Frames 1-13a; Bruce Hall/Asst. Prof. CEH--Frames 14-24; Ann Lemley/Asst. Prof. DEA--Frames 27-36, June 1983; 993; 34 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #3: Ranky Kirk/HSS and teaching assistant, June 1983; 993; 18 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #4: William Trochim/Asst. Prof. HSS, June 1983; 993; 14 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #5: Josephine Allen/Asst. Prof. HSS--Frames 1-10; Melanie Anderson/Computer Literacy Staff member--Frames 11-14; Randy Kirk teaching a summer class about computing and at a computer--Frames 15-17; Maureen Conklin/Sec.-HSS--Frames 81-21, June 1983; 993; 21 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #6: Shelley White-Means, Oct. 1983; 993; 15 (Box 21)
  - Photos of Extension Awareness materials to be used for illustration of article in Extension Review (by Dave Dik & Robert Topor), June 1983; 994; 25 (Box 21)
  - Minority Brochure (descriptions on backs of contacts, including graduation 1983), June 1983; 995; 304 (Box 21)
  - 4-H Congress/MVR, June 1983; 996; 17 (Box 21)
  - EFNEP Photos, Sheet #1: EFNEP aide receiving diploma, June 1983; 997; 21 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #2: EFNEP aide and homemaker in grocery store, June 1983; 997; 10 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #3: EFNEP aide and homemaker in home learning about stir fry cooking, EFNEP aide and homemakers in Cooperative Extension office learning about stir fry cooking, June 1983; 997; 18 (Box 21)
  - Donna Bardell/undergrad in ILR, June 1983; 998; 57 (Box 21)
  - Food Executives Program candids, June 1983; 999; 152 (Box 21)
  - TITLE, DATE; Job #; No of negs (Box 21)
  - Lucinda Noble in her office with Extension Awareness poster and materials, June 1983; 1000; 6 (Box 21)
  - Extension photos for Carol Anderson, Sheet #1: Cooperative Extension agent and children's school teacher discussing programs in front of Preble Children's Center (Eleanor Peavy/Extension Agent and 4-H kids and Ellie in grocery store), June 1983; 1001; 20 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #2: Water testing in lab and computer photos of family (Gordon Webb's family on computer), June 1983; 1001; 18 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #3: Ardie Gillespie talking to phone agents on nutrition--Frames 2-19; 4-H group leader talking on clothes to keep you warm (Sue Cunningham's daughter)-Frames 20-7), June 1983; 1001; 25 (Box 21)
  - CAWFI Conference--Small Business and Third World Food Production, July 8, 1983; 1002; 109 (Box 21)
  - ALS Senior Barbeque, May 1983; 1003; 37 (Box BOX)
  - William Pardee in field and greenhouse--research on corn, June 1983; 1004; 16 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #1: Comstock House, Anna & John Comstock Grave, Comstock Rd. sign, Anna Comstock Hall, Aug. 1983; 1005; 20 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #2: Comstock Hall, New Anna Comstock Hall and Comstock graves, Aug. 1983; 1005; 15 (Box 22)
  - Century Farms-1983, Sheet #1: Delaware County--The Haits Farm, Aug. 1983; 1006; 15 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #2: Musson Farm and Otsego Farm, Sept. 1983; 1006; 14 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #3: Brace Farm in Herkimer County, Sept. 1983; 1006; 14 (Box 22)
  - Campus Scenes, Sheets #1 & 2: McGraw Tower and surrounding areas from top of Statler Inn & Barton Hall, Aug. 1983; 1007; 51 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #3: Photos from roof of Barton Hall, Aug. 1983; 1007; 20 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #4: Photos of front of MVR, Aug. 1983; 1007; 3 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #5: Photos of front of MVR with new picnic tables and students. (for us in news) Warren Hall., Aug. 1983; 1007; 11 +8 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #6: Dyce Lab exterior photos with students in front, Sept. 1983; 1007; 7 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #7: Ag. & Human Ecology/shot by G. Barker, Oct. 1983; 1007; 37 (Box 22)
  - State Fair 1983, Aug. 1983; 1008; 82 (Box 22)
  - New student orientation for HE/Group shots, Aug. 1983; 1009; 7 (Box 22)
  - ALS Roundup, Sept. 1983; 1010; 185 (Box 22)
  - Dr. Alexander in his office and in his lab with associates (Agronomy), Sept. 1983; 1011; 17 (Box 22)
  - Wildlife Damage Control Conference, Sept. 1983; 1012; 22 (Box 22)
  - International Agriculture Programs Twentieth Anniversary, Oct. 10, 1983; 1013; 241 (Box 22)
  - Scholarship donors and recipients, Oct. 1983; 1014; 44 (Box 22)
  - Humphrey Fellows (see list enclosed), Oct. 1983; 1015; 52 (Box 22)
  - ASTM Student Association Textiles Club--Frames 1-7; Vivian White/DEA-Frames 8-12, Oct. 1983; 1016; 12 (Box 22)
  - David Dik & Katherine Giacomi at Apple Computer, Oct. 1983; 1017; 36 (Box 22)
  - Visiting Legislators--Journal Public Hearing for the Senate Ag. Committee and the Assembly Ag. Committee, Oct. 1983; 1018; 48 (Box 22)
  - Check presentation for George Lehocky and Wilcox Dining Room candids, Oct. 1983; 1019; 8 (Box 22)
  - Human Ecology Annual Report, Sheet #1: Family Life Development Resource Center, Nov. 1983; 1020; 8 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #2: HDFS Grad student/research with children and computers (Dianne Divecha(grad student), Bari Kligerman(Ithaca school teacher), Eric Meek (student)), Nov. 1983; 1020; 21 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #3: DEA Interior Design Class, Ron Beckman, Professor, Nov. 1983; 1020; 30 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #4: HSS Faculty meeting including student representatives, Nov. 1983; 1020; 8 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #5: Dean Ziegler, Janelle Farris & James Davis, Frames 2-19; Allan Wilson, VPY Room, William Sima, DEA Chairman and students--Frames 19a-20, Dogs--Frames 29a-32, Nov. 1983; 1020; 30 (Box 22)
  - Dean David Call and Lt. Governor in meeting--Roberts Hall, Nov. 1983; 1021; 27 (Box 22)
  - Eastman Rice speaking contest in Warren Hall, Nov. 1983; 1022; 6 (Box 22)
  - Human Ecology News. Sheets #1 & 2: Advisory Council Meeting & Alumni Display Case, Nov. 1983; 1023; 62 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #3: Gwen Kudler '84 Human Ecology--Taken in MVR, Nov. 1983; 1023; 10 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #4: Andrew Zakow '84 Human Ecology/Taken in his lab in Savage Hall, Nov. 1983; 1023; 8 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #5: Helen Nelson Symposium in MVR Faculty Lounge, Dec. 1983; 1023; 11 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #6: Carolyn Cook in her office in MVR, Jan. 1984; 1023; 8 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #7: John Trudge--HDFS grad student--Frames 17-21; Cindi Arost--Student Counselor--Frames 30-37; Andra Benson with family--HE Alumni--Frames 17-21, Mar. 1984; 1023; 22 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #8: Catherine Personius in her home in Horseheads, NY, Mar. 1984; 1023; 36 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #9: Carolyn Boegly, Associate Prof. & Prog. Coord. For Cooperative Extension, Mar. 1984; 1023; 7 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #10: Peggy Hart Earle & Husband at Entrepreneur Conference in Statler West Lounge, Apr. 1984; 1023; 8 (Box 22)
  - Sheets #11-14: HE Alumni Breakfast and Dianne Dodge & Nancy Saltford at Faculty Commons/MVR, June 1984; 1023; 78 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #15: Kari Asmus (Human Services Studies), July 1984; 1023; 15 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #16: Marita Dangerfield--"Bridges" editor with Sue Ward, secretary in counseling office, Nov. 1984; 1023; 16 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #17: Emeritus Tea/MVR Faculty Commons, Dec. 1984; 1023; 20 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #18: 2 group photos--one of student group and one of HE Alumni Board, Feb. 1, 1985; 1023; 11 (Box 22)
  - Soil Judging Team/Agronomy taken in Bradfield Hall, TA in Ag. School, Nov. 11, 1983; 1024; 4 (Box 22)
  - Display for Roberts Hall, Sheet #1: Education in 110 class in Stone Hall--Gary L. Canter teaching, Nov. 1983; 1025; 27 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #2: Comm. Arts 221 & Floriculture--Mann Library & Plant Sciences, Dec. 1983; 1025; 26 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #3: Animal Science 221 & Comm. Arts 200--Microbiology class, Dec. 1983; 1025; 35 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #4: Ag. Economics 220--Biology 101 & Animal Science 221--TA is Kay Hughes, Dec. 1983; 1025; 36 (Box 22)
  - Murray Elliot giving Dairy Days award to David Hardie, Jan. 10, 1984; 1026; 13 (Box 22)
  - Large Animal Research Teaching Unit general photos, Feb. 1984; 1027; 23 (Box 22)
  - Grossingers/Technology Fair, Jan. 1984; 1028; 184 (Box 22)
  - Joan Spielholz inspecting beehive in Guterman Lab; Pollination experiment with alfalfa, Feb. 10, 1984; 1029; 31 (Box 22)
  - Photos of Pitney Bowes sorting machine at Research Park and mailing machine in B10 MVR. Photos for Rath Organization, Feb. 27, 1984; 1030; 12 (Box 22)
  - Entomology Faculty, Mar. 1984; 1031; 81 (Box 22)
  - Home Study Faculty group and stills of Home Study books, Mar. 1984; 1032; 9 (Box 22)
  - New agents for 1984/Jane McGonigal/Cooperative Extension, Mar. 1984; 1033; 47 (Box 22)
  - Extension Conference for student recruitment in Human Ecology, Mar. 1984; 1034; 37 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #1: Ron Gorewit--Associate Prof. Of Animal Science using computer and reading data (F & LSQ), Mar. 1984; 1035; 37 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #2: Computer & Farm scenes/Millbrook Farm (Space Farm) & Mike Heksler (Ag. Engineering), Mar. 1984; 1035; No. of Negs: (Box 22)
  - BTI Annual Report, Apr. 1984; 1036; 13 (Box 22)
  - Ag. Day, Mar. 1984; 1037; 37 (Box 22)
  - Nutritional Science Alumni meeting and Nut. Sci. Lab scenes tour for Alumni-Dr. Zilversmith's lab; Colin Campbell's lab, Dr. Rasmussen's lab; and Meta Unit in Savage Hall; David Ayellod, Mar. 1984; 1038; No. of Negs: (Box 22)
  - HE Activities--taken for use in HE Search Mailer, Winter 1984; 1039; 227 (Box 22)
  - Strawberries and Cream Faraiche; Buttermilk pouring into glass; Cucumbers and sour crème, Apr. 1984; 1040; 8 (Box 22)
  - Edward L. Bernays visit to Cornell Campus, Apr. 1984; 1041; 167 (Box 22)
  - John Tompkins & Robert Smock--Pomology, May 1984; 1042; 8 (Box 22)
  - Annual Scholarship Reception--Held in Warren Hall, May 1984; 1043; 23 (Box 22)
  - Campus Scenes, Sheet #1: A.D. White House, Red Barn, MVR, Sage Hall, Spring 1984; 1044; 10 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #2: Students & Computers at Mann Micro-computer Ctr., May 1984; 1044; 38 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #3: Sage Hall & Sage Chapel, May 1984; 1044; 4 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #4: 1984 Graduation--Photos from Clock Tower, May 1984; 1044; 13 (Box 22)
  - Watkins Salt Company Well #1 and street scenes of Watkins Glen, NY taken for Watkins Glen Business Directory, May 1984; 1045; 17 (Box 22)
  - Photos of Statue of Ezra Cornell for Computer Services Exhibit, May 1984; 1046; 12 (Box 22)
  - State Fair 1984, Sheet #1: Campus scenes taken by James Mason to test camera--Robert Hall, Lou Mins Gardens, College of Ag. Corner stone, May 1984; 1047; 35 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #2: Gov. Cuomo at Ag. Exhibit in Ag. & Health Bldg./State Fair, Sept. 1984; 1047; 35 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #3: Interior shots of Ag. & Health Bldg. before the Ag. Exhibit was set up for display, Aug. 1984; 1047; 16 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #4: Kenneth Wing at Ag. Exhibit and various shots of people looking at the exhibit, Aug. 1984; 1047; 36 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #5: Kenneth Wing talking with Gov. Cuomo's wife, Aug. 1984; 1047; 10 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #6: Lucinda Noble receiving award at State Fair & candid shots at fair of various activities, Aug. 1984; 1047; 36 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #7: Cotton Hanlon Co. harvesting timber near Moravia, NY 2 1/4 x 2 1/4 color negs, July 1984; 1047; 12 (Box 22)
  - Student profiles for Sally Dutko and Jennifer Hughes, May 1984; 1048; 54 (Box 22)
  - Lucinda Noble/Director of Extension at her desk and in her office in Roberts Hall, May 1984; 1049; 32 (Box 22)
  - Sheets #1 & 2: Field Study student working with elderly at Tompkins County Senior Citizens Center (Robin Secord), May 1984; 1050; 36 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #3: Field Study student at Youth Center talking to teens and giving presentation (Claire Myer), May 1984; 1050; 15 (Box 22)
  - Field Study Class also on sheet #3, May 1984; 1050; 6 (Box 22)
  - Highway School, June 1984; 1051; 44 (Box 22)
  - Retirement party for Clara Straight/Prof. DEA and Regina Rector/Extension Associate DEA, June 1984; 1052; 24 (Box 22)
  - Ag. Senior Barbeque, June 1984; 1053; No. of Negs: (Box 22)
  - Summer Fellowship students in meeting main speakers were George Broadwell, Barbara Eshelman, Bill Worth, June 1984; 1054; 37 (Box 22)
  - Human Ecology Forum, Sheet #1: Dryden Head Start visits Doug Barton Farm on Irish Settlement Road, Dryden, NY, June 1984; 1055; 37 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #2: Susan Watkins in her lab, Aug. 1984; 1055; 26 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #3: Robert Harris/Asso. Prof. in his office at Africana Center, Aug. 1984; 1055; 7 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #4: Sam Sappington, Counselor in HE with Robert Heasley--grad student, Jan. 1985; 1055; 17 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #5: Patti Morris--grad student HE Nutritional Sciences, Mar. 1986; 1055; 20 (Box 22)
  - Cooperative Extension Awareness Program, Sheet #1: 4-H Club Dog Show (Junior Tail Diggers), June 1984; 1056; 36 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #2: 4-H Computer Club with music professor showing them computerized music at Ithaca College, Ford Hall, June 1984; 1056; 20 (Box 22)
  - Large Animal Research /Teaching Unit activities, June 1984; 1057; 62 (Box 22)
  - Ag. Business Executive Program candids, June 1984; 1058; 21 (Box 22)
  - Ag. Alumni Breakfast, June 1984; 1059; 70 (Box 22)
  - "Your Link with Cornell" exhibit for Glenna Thaylor, June 1984; 1060; 15 (Box 22)
  - Minority Student Reception (HE Annual Report), June 13, 1984; 1061; 67 (Box 22)
  - Health Executive Development Program, Management Group Seminars (HE Annual Report), June 1984; 1062; 68 (Box 22)
  - Sheet #1: Conferences in MVR June 21, June 1984; 1063; 9 (Box 22)